chasingthedonkey.com 2019-06-20

# Chasing the Donkey: Privacy Policy & Disclaimers

######  Some posts contain compensated links. Please read [this disclaimer](https://www.chasingthedonkey.com/privacy-policy/) for more info.

## © Please Don’t Steal My Hard Work

Therefore do not republish any of the content found on this blog without permission. Excerpts of my article may be used, provided a link back to the original URL is used, and that full and clear credit is given to us here at Chasing the Donkey. You can contact us using our contact form anytime, and we can make other arrangements (have your cheque book at the ready)

## Important FTC disclosure

There are lots of affiliate links on Chasing the Donkey, and when you click on them and buy something, I’ll make a small commission. But, don’t worry, there are no extra charges to you.

I do not recommend products unless I believe they are of value for you and I believe in them. Earning a commission is a nice side benefit which allows me to keep traveling and writing great content/

chasingthedonkey.com is owned and operated by Begonja doo. and may contain advertisements, sponsored content, paid insertions, affiliate links or other forms of monetization.

chasingthedonkey.com abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. Any content where we receive money for talking about it **will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.**

Chasing the Donkey is never directly compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this website are purely those of the authors. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

Chasing the Donkey makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency or completeness of the content contain on this website or any sites linked to or from this site. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website. Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Chasing the Donkey. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Chasing the Donkey takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

## Affiliates

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

Also, many posts on this site contain affiliate links to accommodation and activity booking sites, which means at no extra cost to you if you make a booking, I receive a commission.

## **Privacy**

This privacy policy sets out how Chasing the Donkey uses and protects any information that you give while using www.chasingthedonkey.com

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**Chasing the Donkey may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 2015 and was updated in May 2018 to comply with GDPR.**

We are not liable as to the accuracy or validity of any information provided.  We are not liable for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use.

## **Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. We record cookies for 26 months. **If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit  [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.**

This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes, and then the data is removed from the system after 26 months.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

The list below describes the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently, we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari, etc.)

**First Party Cookies**

These are cookies that are set by this website directly.

**Google Analytics:**  We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behavior on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our website and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We, therefore, do not collect or store your personal information (e.g., your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html>

**WordPress:**  Our websites runs the popular WordPress CMS and cookies are used to store basic data on your interactions with WordPress, and whether you have logged into WordPress. We use a  **session cookie**  to remember your log-in for you if you are a registered user and we deem these as being strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled, then various functionality on the site will be broken.

More information on session cookies and what they are used for at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/session-cookies-used-for.html>

**Third Party Cookies**

These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by  **LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, Google+ and Pinterest**. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.

You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out or delete such information

## Travel Information

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Chasing the Doney and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

## Email Subscriptions

We’re committed to protecting your privacy. Under no circumstances will we sell, rent or trade any information that visitors to the site or newsletter subscribers provide. Ever. So please don’t even ask.

## **Disclosure**

We always explicitly indicated in the article which items or services reviewed we done so in exchange for the article. Always. If you don’t see a disclosure, then we paid for the good or service.

## 

**Comments are welcomed and encouraged** , but there are some instances where comments will be edited or deleted as follows:

  1. Comments deemed to be spam, or questionable spam will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted, but comments should be relevant to the post topic.
  2. Comments including profanity will be deleted.
  3. Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive will be deleted.
  4. Comments that attack a person individually will be deleted.

We reserve the right to edit or delete any comments submitted to this blog without notice.

## **What We Collect**

We may collect the following information:

  1. contact information including email address
  2. demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests
  3. other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## **What We Do With The Information We Gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

## **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## **Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website.  These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

You can find more about advertisers privacy policies from our partner [here](https://www.mediavine.com/gdpr/).

## **Links To Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## **Controlling Your Personal Information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  1. whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  2. if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time at **croatia@chasingthedonkey.com**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
